<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Connecting With Being</string>

    <!-- Main Activity Strings-->
    <string name = "main_activity_title">Connecting With...</string>
    <string name= "about_activity_title">About</string>
    <string name = "contact_activity_title">Contacts</string>
    <string name = "settings_activity_title">Settings</string>
    <string name = "credits_activity_title">Credits</string>
    <string name = "quote_text_placeholder">\"Quotes For Each Exercise Go Here\"</string>

    <string name="open">open toggle</string>
    <string name="close">close toggle</string>
    <string name="home_button_toast">You are already home!</string>
    <string name="exercise_completed_default">"X 0/6"</string>
    <string name="question_default_string">Question goes here</string>

    <string name="exercise1_center_text_string">Go in nature by yourself with no predetermined route (or very minimal one) or length of time. What was the most exciting thing that happened during that walk? Were you thinking a lot? Or not at all? What was in your head?</string>
    <string name="exercise2_center_text_string">Pick an artistic medium you are not comfortable with and just create. Try not to judge or compare yourself to others!</string>
    <string name="exercise1_questions_button_string">Reflection</string>

    <!-- Introduction Strings-->

    <string name="introduction_text">"Based on environmental education and various philosophical concepts, this app invites you to explore your relationship with yourself, others, nature, and society. It aims at creating a deeper connection with the world inside and around you.

Through exercises and introspective questions, you will be challenged to get out of your comfort zone and free yourself from some of the more hindering assumptions of modern life. Focus on the process, there are no “good or bad answers”, it is all about your personal growth.

These exercises involve you to take actions with yourself, others and nature. Therefore, be safe, responsible, and kind with any interaction towards yourself or the outside world! Remember to have fun and to be curious and open-minded!

We humbly hope that this will make at least a slight difference in your life (even for a microsecond!), and that you’ll enjoy being part of the movement towards a more sustainable and compassionate world."</string>

    <string name="ui_title">How To Use The App</string>
    <string name="ui_instructions">The functionality of the app is pretty simple. All of the icons below can be clicked on for navigation. Click on each icon to learn more.</string>
    <string name= "ui_menu_icon">Opens up the exercise menu for the selected category. In this case the category is Nature. The star count below the image keeps track of how many exercises you\'ve completed.</string>
    <string name="ui_menu_icon_title">Open Exercise Menu Button</string>
    <string name="ui_exercise_icon">Starts the selected exercise. When the exercise is completed the star turns gold. You can also long click the exercise to reset the star.</string>
    <string name="ui_exercise_icon_title">Start Exercise Button</string>
    <string name = "ui_home_icon">A basic home button that allows you to access the home menu.</string>
    <string name ="ui_home_icon_title">Home Button</string>
    <string name="ui_shuffle_icon">The shuffle icon will randomly select and start an exercise for you.</string>
    <string name ="ui_shuffle_icon_title">Shuffle Button</string>
    <string name="ui_bookmark_icon">The bookmark icon will save the current exercise for later, or load the saved exercise when on the home screen.</string>
    <string name="ui_bookmark_icon_title">Bookmark Button</string>
    <string name="ui_info_icon">The info icon will let you know which category and exercise you are currently on.</string>
    <string name="ui_info_icon_title">Info Button</string>



    <!-- Self Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="self_menu_title">With Self…</string>

    <string name="self_e1_title">Create For the Experience</string>
    <string name="self_e1_quote">"\"If you hear a voice within you say 'you cannot paint,' then by all means paint, and that voice will be silenced\"

- Vincent Van Gogh"
</string>
    <string name="self_e1_text">Pick an artistic medium you are not comfortable with and just try … Create!</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q1_text">Were you scared at all to start creating? Did you judge yourself? Why or why not?</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q2_text">Did you have a preconception of what is good art? What does creativity mean to you?</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e2_title">Dance, Dance, Dance!</string>
    <string name="self_e2_quote">"\"I don't do well with snakes and I can't dance.\"

- Robin Williams"
</string>
    <string name="self_e2_text">Be alone. Listen to your favorite songs and dance to them anyway you want!</string>
    <string name="self_e2_q1_text">How comfortable were you about moving your body to the music? What parts of your body did you move the most?</string>
    <string name="self_e2_q2_text">Did you think at all while you were dancing? Did you lose track of time? How long did you dance for?</string>
    <string name="self_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e3_title">Dreams Are What We’re Made Of</string>
    <string name="self_e3_quote">"\"My dreams were all my own; I accounted for them to nobody; they were my refuge when annoyed - my dearest pleasure when free.\"

- Mary Shelley"
</string>
    <string name="self_e3_text">What were your dreams for the future (about what or who you wanted to be) when you were younger? And what are your dreams right now?</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q1_text">How similar or different were your dreams when you were young to ones you have today?</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q2_text">What influenced your dreams when you were younger? What influences your current dreams now?</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e4_title">Defining Yourself</string>
    <string name="self_e4_quote">"\"An identity would seem to be arrived at by the way in which the person faces and uses his experience.\"

- James Baldwin"
</string>
    <string name="self_e4_text">Write down a list of single words that define you until you can’t easily think of anymore. Don’t overthink it, write whatever comes to your mind.</string>
    <string name="self_e4_q1_text">Could you categorize the words that describe you into: hobbies, values, roles, qualities …
</string>
    <string name="self_e4_q2_text">At what point could you no longer describe yourself? What final words did you land on?</string>
    <string name="self_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e5_title">Surf Your Vibe</string>
    <string name="self_e5_quote">"\"Men do not quit playing because they grow old; they grow old because they quit playing.\"

- Oliver Wendell Holmes, Sr."
</string>
    <string name="self_e5_text">What is your favorite hobby? Take some time today (or as soon as you can!) to participate in your favorite activity.</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q1_text">What do you like best about your hobby? Try to describe the different aspects of the activity that you enjoy.</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q2_text">Would you like to do it more? What stops you if that’s the case? Could you make the time somewhere?</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e6_title">Your Story</string>
    <string name="self_e6_quote">"\"Our stories come from our lives and from the playwright's pen, the mind of the actor, the roles we create, the artistry of life itself and the quest for peace.\"

- Maya Angelou"
</string>
    <string name="self_e6_text">Let’s pretend there is a book about your life. How would the cover look? What would the title of the book be? What about the names of the different chapters?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q1_text">What genre is your story? Drama? Mystery? Romance? Adventure? Tragedy? Comedy?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q2_text">All good stories have a central conflict that the hero must overcome. What is your central conflict?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


    <!--Others Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="others_menu_title">With Others...</string>

    <string name="others_e1_title">Difference of Opinions</string>
    <string name="others_e1_quote">"Others Exercise 1 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e1_text">"Find someone of your entourage that has a different political or social point of view of yours on a specific topic and just listen. Try to understand how they came to their conclusions. </string>
    <string name="others_e1_q1_text">What was your initial internal reaction to their points of view? How did you feel? Was it hard not to immediately try to counter their opinions?</string>
    <string name="others_e1_q2_text">Did you gain any new perspectives on the matter? Could you feel empathy with someone you disagree with?</string>
    <string name="others_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e2_title">Handwriting a surprise-letter</string>
    <string name="others_e2_quote">"Others Exercise 2 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e2_text">Think about someone you appreciate and value a lot. Take the time to hand write a letter to let them know why, and what you appreciate about them. There’s never too much love to share and receive. Stamp your letter, drop it off at the nearest post office, and away it goes!</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q1_text">Did you feel a difference writing a letter by hand rather than email, text, or digital technologies?</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q2_text">What was the recipient\'s reaction to receiving the letter? Did they also find novelty in a handwritten letter?</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e3_title">Different Small Talk</string>
    <string name="others_e3_quote">"Others Exercise 3 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e3_text">Next time you bump into a stranger or somebody you don’t know very well, (in the street, at your workplace, at the supermarket) switch from the typical “Hi! How are you?” to “Hi! So what was the best thing that happened in your day so far?”</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q1_text">What was the reaction of the person? What was his\her answer? What have you learned about that person?</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q2_text">And what about you? What is the best thing that happened to you today?</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


    <string name="others_e4_title">Meet your neighbors</string>
    <string name="others_e4_quote">"Others Exercise 4 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e4_text">Do you know your neighbors? If you know your close neighbors, what about the ones two doors away ? Knock on their door and introduce yourself!</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q1_text">Was it a short conversation or did it lead to something more than you were expecting?</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q2_text">When you see them out and about next time, will you wave and say hello if it feels good to do so?</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e5_title">The Elders</string>
    <string name="others_e5_quote">"Others Exercise 5 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e5_text">Go to a retirement house and speak to an elderly person about his/her life. Ask them about their best childhood memories. What adventures did they have in their youth? Middle age?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q1_text">How was your experience? What were the conversations about?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q2_text">What is your perception of elderly people in your society? Did that perception change?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e6_title">Om mani padme hum..</string>
    <string name="others_e6_quote">"Others Exercise 6 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="others_e6_text">Attend a religious ceremony of a different faith than your own.</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q1_text">"What have your other experiences with spiritual practices been like? How did you feel during this particular ceremony? How was it similar or different to your past experiences? What aspects of the ceremony did you find most enlightening?"</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q2_text">How were your interactions with the community? Was there anyone you felt a special connection with?</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


    <!--Nature Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="nature_menu_title">With Nature...</string>

    <string name="nature_e1_title">Hug A Tree!</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_quote">"Nature Quote One"</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_text">"Find the most inspiring tree around your area, and give it a big hug.

While you’re there take a long breath, and thank that tree for the air you are breathing."
    </string>
    <string name="nature_e1_q1_text">Was it your first experience of hugging a tree? How did you feel?</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_q2_text">How do you feel about doing this exercise in public?</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection to nature? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="nature_e2_title">Walk Solo in Nature</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_quote">"\"The clearest way into the Universe is through a forest wilderness.\"
- John Muir"</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_text">Go in nature by yourself with no predetermined route (or very minimal one) or length of time.</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_q1_text">What was the most exciting thing that happened during that walk?</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_q2_text">Were you thinking a lot or not at all? What was in your head?</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_title">Nature as a Child</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_quote">"\"And this, our life, exempt from public haunt, finds tongues in trees, books in the running brooks, sermons in stones, and good in everything.\"
-William Shakespeare"
</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_text">Try to remember a memory from your childhood that you felt particularly connected with nature. Where was it? Who were with you? What were you doing?</string>
    <string name="nature_e3_q1_text">What was the importance of nature during your childhood?</string>
    <string name="nature_e3_q2_text">How did this memory or that particular place shape the relationship that you now have with nature?</string>
    <string name="nature_e3_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e4_title">Do the Earth a Favor!</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_quote">"Society Exercise 4 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_text">Walk around your local park or neighborhood and pick up a single piece of trash (or more!) off the ground. Make sure it finds its way to the proper bin! (Remember to compost or recycle if you can.)</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_q1_text">Did you notice a lot (or very little) trash where you were walking? What was your initial reaction to the presence of or lack of trash in your immediate surroundings?</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_q2_text">How did you feel carrying around someone else’s trash? When it made it to the bin, what was the first feeling that you had?</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e5_title">The Elements</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_quote">"Nature Exercise 5 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_text">Connect mindfully with the four elements using all your senses. The four elements are Earth, Water, Fire and Air. For example, silence your thoughts, and stare at a lit candle, feel the soil with your bare feet, listen to the wind, and smell the ocean.</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_q1_text">Which element did you feel the most connected to? Why?</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_q2_text">Which sense did you naturally use the most to connect with each element?</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e6_title">Adopt a Pet Plant!</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_quote">"Nature Exercise 6 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_text">Find a small plant that is seeding in a park, or in the woods. Gently up root it, and grab some of the soil that it was growing in. Bring it home, put it into a cup or jar, try to identify the species and its basic needs, and see what happens! You now have a new friend!</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_q1_text">Why did you choose this plant? What attracted you to that particular plant?</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_q2_text">Do you feel any emotional connection with the plant now that it’s home? Did you give it a name?</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <!-- Society Exercises Strings -->
    <string name="society_menu_title">With Society...</string>

    <string name="society_e1_title">Disconnect and Unplug</string>
    <string name="society_e1_quote">"Society Exercise 1 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="society_e1_text">Try to spend just one day (safely!) without your phone. Bonus points if you are actually still in the city, and not in the woods somewhere.</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q1_text">What was your initial reaction? Did you feel stress?  Freedom?</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q2_text">When you got back on the grid, what was it like to use your device again?
</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e2_title">The Role of Money</string>
    <string name="society_e2_quote">"Society Exercise 2 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="society_e2_text">Think of your relationship with money. Focus on your feelings around it, and your initial emotional reaction to your current financial situation.</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q1_text">What is more important to you than money? What would you not give up for any price in the world?</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q2_text">What would you consider “enough”? How big would your bank account have to be that when you see it, you feel safe and free to take opportunities?</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e3_title">Represent Local</string>
    <string name="society_e3_quote">"Society Exercise 3 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="society_e3_text">"Local and state governments often have a much bigger effect on your life than federal. Attend a local city council meeting, or watch a session of your state congress.
        Attempt to meet your city council or state government representative. Is there any important local issue you could talk with them about?"</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q1_text">What issues did they discuss? Was there anything about the process that stood out to you?</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q2_text">Did you like your representative? How could you work with them to address the issues you feel concerned about?</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e4_title">Kindness on the Street</string>
    <string name="society_e4_quote">"Society Exercise 4 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="society_e4_text">Give a person in need some change or food. Ask them their name, and wish them a good day.</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q1_text">What was their reaction? Did their demeanor change once you asked for their name?</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q2_text">How did you feel after the interaction was over? Was there a sense of doing some good?</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e5_title">Every Bit Counts</string>
    <string name="society_e5_quote">"Society Exercise 5 Quote Holder"</string>
    <string name="society_e5_text">Sign up to make a small monthly donation (about the cost of a lunch, whatever you can afford) to a charity that advocates for a cause that you support. Any cause will do! A monthly donation makes you a real member of these organizations.</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q1_text">How do you feel about giving to a cause on a regular basis?</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q2_text">Do you think you’ll participate or become more involved with the issue over time?</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e6_title">Do Good Works</string>
    <string name="society_e6_quote">"\"What is the essence of life? To serve others and to do good.\"
-Aristotle"</string>
    <string name="society_e6_text">A tried and true classic to feel good and meet great people! Find a cause and organization you care about, and volunteer for a day. Even if it’s just once, you certainly won’t forget the experience.</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q1_text">Where did you choose to volunteer? What was the work like?</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q2_text">Did you build good relationships? Did you feel connected with the other volunteers? Your community as a whole?</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


</resources>
