<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Be You</string>

    <!-- Main Activity Strings-->
    <string name="welcome_screen_title">..~~**Engage**~~..</string>
    <string name = "main_activity_title">Connecting With...</string>
    <string name= "about_activity_title">About Engage With Being</string>
    <string name = "contact_activity_title">Contacts</string>
    <string name = "settings_activity_title">Settings</string>
    <string name = "credits_activity_title">Credits</string>
    <string name = "quote_activity_title">Your Daily Quote</string>
    <string name = "quote_text_placeholder">\"Quotes For Each Exercise Go Here\"</string>
    <string name = "questions_activity_title">Reflections</string>

    <!-- Menu Strings -->
    <string name="about_string">"Based on environmental education and various philosophical concepts, this app invites you to explore your relationship with yourself, others, nature, and society. It aims at creating a deeper connection with the world inside and around you.

Through exercises and introspective questions, you will be challenged to get out of your comfort zone, and question some behaviors or assumptions that you may have about the modern world. Once the exercise is completed, you will be asked some questions to deepen your awareness and your reflections. This App aims to be a fun way to explore the connections with yourself and the World. This App does not pretend to have any answers, but seeks to shine a light on some of our behaviors. There are no “good or bad answers”, it is all about your subjectivity and your personal growth.

These exercises involve you to take actions with yourself, others and nature. Therefore, be safe, responsible, and kind with any interaction towards yourself or the outside world!
Remember to have fun and to be curious and open-minded

There are four categories:
Self, Others, Nature and Society.
Each exercise is classified under one category although the four categories are intertwined.

The descriptions for each category are as follows.
Self: This category explores the relationship with different aspects of yourself, such as physical, emotional, spiritual, psychological, and so on. How can you be true to who you are, and emancipate yourself?

Others: This category explores your unique relationship with the people around you such as your family, your friends, and the people in your community. How can we grow gratitude and compassion for Others?

Nature: This category explores your relationship with the natural world with an ecocentric and eco philosophical perspective. How can we change our attitude and grow affection toward Nature?

Society: This category explores your relationship with the norms, values, and structures of our society (Western). Why do we do the things we do, looking through the lens of Society?

We humbly hope that this will make at least a slight difference in your life, and that you’ll enjoy being part of the movement towards a more sustainable and compassionate world."
</string>

    <string name="credits_string_1">All images provide by www.flaticon.com

Icons made by <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/authors/freepik" title="Freepik">Freepik</a> from <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/" title="Flaticon"> www.flaticon.com</a>
    </string>


    <string name="credits_string_2">"Some of the books and other references that have influenced this App:

Philosophize This! By Steven West
https://www.philosophizethis.org/

Active Hope by Joanna Macy and Chris Johnstone
https://www.activehope.info/

Sacred Economics by Charles Eisenstein
https://sacred-economics.com/

Toward a Transpersonal Ecology by Warwick Fox
https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/2131870.Toward_a_Transpersonal_Ecology"
    </string>

    <string name="contacts_string">"For more questions, comments, or more information, please email rayadevinfo@gmail.com.

We’ll get back to you as soon as we can!"
</string>


    <!--Alert Dialog Strings-->
    <string name = "intro_complete_title">Introduction Completed!</string>
    <string name = "intro_complete_text">Continue to the main menu?</string>

    <string name = "exercise_complete_title">Continue to Reflections?</string>
    <string name = "exercise_complete_text">Have you completed the exercise?</string>

    <string name = "questions_complete_title">Finish Reflecting?</string>
    <string name = "questions_complete_text">Have you thought about all the questions?</string>

    <string name ="yes">Yes!</string>
    <string name = "dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name ="take_more_time">Take more time</string>

    <string name="open">open toggle</string>
    <string name="close">close toggle</string>>
    <string name="home_button_toast">You are already home!</string>
    <string name="exercise_completed_default">"X 0/6"</string>
    <string name="question_default_string">Question goes here</string>

    <string name="exercise1_center_text_string">Go in nature by yourself with no predetermined route (or very minimal one) or length of time. What was the most exciting thing that happened during that walk? Were you thinking a lot? Or not at all? What was in your head?</string>
    <string name="exercise2_center_text_string">Pick an artistic medium you are not comfortable with and just create. Try not to judge or compare yourself to others!</string>
    <string name="exercise1_questions_button_string">Reflection</string>

    <!-- Introduction Strings-->
    <string name="intro_text_simple">"Based on environmental education and various philosophical concepts, ~~**Engage With Being**~~ invites you to explore your relationship with yourself, others, nature, and society. It aims at creating a deeper connection with the world inside and around you.

Through exercises and introspective questions, you will be challenged to get out of your comfort zone and examine your beliefs about various aspects of modern life. Focus on the process, there are no “good or bad answers”, it is all about your personal growth!

Click on the blinking next icon below to learn how to use the app."
</string>

    <string name="introduction_text">"Based on environmental education and various philosophical concepts, this app invites you to explore your relationship with yourself, others, nature, and society. It aims at creating a deeper connection with the world inside and around you.

Through exercises and introspective questions, you will be challenged to get out of your comfort zone and free yourself from some of the more hindering assumptions of modern life. Focus on the process, there are no “good or bad answers”, it is all about your personal growth.

These exercises involve you to take actions with yourself, others and nature. Therefore, be safe, responsible, and kind with any interaction towards yourself or the outside world! Remember to have fun and to be curious and open-minded!

We humbly hope that this will make at least a slight difference in your life (even for a microsecond!), and that you’ll enjoy being part of the movement towards a more sustainable and compassionate world."</string>

    <string name="ui_title">How To Use The App</string>
    <string name="ui_instructions">The functionality of the app is pretty simple. Navigation is controlled by a few key buttons. Read the description below, then click each blinking icon to progress.</string>
    <string name= "ui_menu_icon">Opens up the Exercise Menu for the selected category. In this case the category is Nature. The star count below the image keeps track of how many exercises you\'ve completed.</string>
    <string name="ui_menu_icon_title">Open Exercise Menu Button</string>
    <string name="ui_exercise_icon">Starts the Selected Exercise. When the exercise is completed the star turns gold. You can also long click the exercise to reset the star.</string>
    <string name="ui_exercise_icon_title">Start Exercise Button</string>
    <string name = "ui_home_icon">A basic Home Button that allows you to access the home menu from anywhere in the app.</string>
    <string name ="ui_home_icon_title">Home Button</string>
    <string name="ui_shuffle_icon">The Shuffle Button will randomly select and start an exercise for you.</string>
    <string name ="ui_shuffle_icon_title">Shuffle Button</string>
    <string name="ui_bookmark_icon">The Bookmark Button will save the current exercise for later, or load the saved exercise when on the home screen.</string>
    <string name="ui_bookmark_icon_title">Bookmark Button</string>
    <string name="ui_info_icon">The Info Button will let you know which category and exercise you are currently on.</string>
    <string name="ui_info_icon_title">Info Button</string>
    <string name="ui_next_button_text">Your essential Next Button. Controls all forward navigation through the app.</string>


    <!-- Self Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="self_home_title">Self</string>
    <string name="self_menu_title">With Self…</string>

    <string name="self_e1_title">A Flow of Creativity</string>
    <string name="self_e1_quote">"\"If you hear a voice within you say 'you cannot paint,' then by all means paint, and that voice will be silenced.\"

- Vincent Van Gogh, Painter"
</string>
    <string name="self_e1_text">Pick an artistic medium you are not comfortable with and just try … Create!</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q1_text">Were you scared at all to start creating? Did you judge yourself? Why or why not?</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q2_text">Did you have a preconception of what good art is? What does creativity mean to you?</string>
    <string name="self_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e2_title">Lose Yourself to Dance!</string>

    <string name="self_e2_quote">"\"Dancing is creating a sculpture that is visible only for a moment.\"

- Erol Ozan, Salsa Dancer"
</string>

    <string name="self_e2_text">Be alone, create a comfortable space, and play your favorite songs. Dance to them anyway you want!</string>

    <string name="self_e2_q1_text">How comfortable were you about moving your body to the music? What parts of your body did you move the most?</string>
    <string name="self_e2_q2_text">Did you think at all while you were dancing? How long did you dance for? Did you lose track of time?</string>
    <string name="self_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e3_title">We’re Made Of Dreams</string>
    <string name="self_e3_quote">"\"So many of our dreams at first seem impossible, then they seem improbable, and then, when we summon the will, they soon become inevitable.\"

- Christopher Reeve, Actor"
</string>

    <string name="self_e3_text">"First, write down the dreams you had when you were younger, about what or who you wanted to become when you grow up.

Then, write down your current dreams about what you want to do or become in the future."</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q1_text">Have you fulfilled some of your dreams from when you were younger?</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q2_text">How similar or different were the dreams from your younger days to the ones that you have now?</string>
    <string name="self_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e4_title">The Power of Words</string>
    <string name="self_e4_quote">"\"Your words become your world.\"

- Nadeem Kazi, Author"
</string>

    <string name="self_e4_text">"Write down a list of single words that define you until you can’t easily think of anymore.

Don’t overthink it, write whatever comes to your mind."</string>

    <string name="self_e4_q1_text">How many words did you end up with? What was the first and final word that you wrote to describe yourself?</string>
    <string name="self_e4_q2_text">Categorize the words that describe you. Do they fall into hobbies, values, roles you have in the society, qualities or physical characteristics? How many words do you have for each category?</string>
    <string name="self_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e5_title">Surf Your Vibe</string>
    <string name="self_e5_quote">"\"We do not quit playing because we grow old; we grow old because we quit playing.\"

- George Bernard Shaw, Playwright"
</string>

    <string name="self_e5_text">What is your favorite hobby? Take some time today (or as soon as you can!) to participate in your favorite activity.</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q1_text">What do you like best about your hobby? Try to describe the different aspects of the activity that you enjoy.</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q2_text">Would you like to do it more? What stops you if that’s the case? Could you make the time somewhere?</string>
    <string name="self_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="self_e6_title">Your Story</string>
    <string name="self_e6_quote">"\"Your life becomes the story you tell yourself. Change the story you tell. Change your life.\"

- Karen Salmansohn, Author"
</string>

    <string name="self_e6_text">Let’s pretend you are the main character of a novel, and it is about your current life. What is the main plot, the central conflict? Who are your main allies and your main enemies? How would the cover look? What would the title of the book be?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q1_text">Which elements of the story, if any, would you like to change? Why or why not?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q2_text">What would the resolution of your book look like? How would the conflicts be resolved?</string>
    <string name="self_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with yourself? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


    <!--Others Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="others_home_title">Others</string>
    <string name="others_menu_title">With Others...</string>

    <string name="others_e1_title">Difference of Opinions</string>
    <string name="others_e1_quote">"\"Most of all, differences of opinion are opportunities for learning.\"

- Terry Tempest Williams, Educator</string>
    <string name="others_e1_text">"Find someone of your entourage that has a different political or social point of view of yours on a specific topic and just listen without giving your opinion.

Try to understand how they came to form their opinion, and how their circumstances and environment influenced their perspective."
</string>

    <string name="others_e1_q1_text">What was your initial internal reaction to their points of view? How did you feel? Was it hard not to immediately try to counter their opinions?</string>
    <string name="others_e1_q2_text">Did you gain any new perspectives on the matter? Could you feel empathy with someone you disagree with?</string>
    <string name="others_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e2_title">Surprise-letter!</string>
    <string name="others_e2_quote">"\"A letter always seemed to me like immortality, because it is the mind alone without a corporeal friend.\"

- Emily Dickinson, Poet</string>
    <string name="others_e2_text">Think about someone you appreciate and value a lot! Take the time to hand write a letter to let them know why, and what you appreciate about them. Stamp your letter, drop it off at the nearest post office, and away it goes!</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q1_text">Did you feel a difference writing a letter by hand rather than email, text, or digital technologies?</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q2_text">What was the recipient\'s reaction to receiving the letter? Did they also find novelty in a handwritten letter?</string>
    <string name="others_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e3_title">Different Small Talk</string>
    <string name="others_e3_quote">"\"I want to speak, to sing to total strangers. It’s my way of talking to the world.\"

-Adrian Mitchell, Poet</string>
    <string name="others_e3_text">Next time you bump into a stranger or somebody you don’t know very well, (in the street, at your workplace, at the supermarket) switch from the typical “Hi! How are you?” to “Hi! So what was the best thing that happened in your day so far?”</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q1_text">What was the reaction of the person? What was their answer? What have you learned about that person?</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q2_text">And what about you? What is the best thing that happened to you today?</string>
    <string name="others_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>


    <string name="others_e4_title">Howdy Neighbor!</string>
    <string name="others_e4_quote">"\"Being a good neighbor is an art which make life richer.\"

 - Gladys Taber, Author"</string>
    <string name="others_e4_text">Do you know your neighbors? If you know your close neighbors, what about the ones two doors away ? Knock on their door and introduce yourself! Think about how you could offer them your help someday and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q1_text">Was it a short conversation or did it lead to something more than you were expecting?</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q2_text">When you see them out and about next time, will you wave and say hello if it feels good to do so?</string>
    <string name="others_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e5_title">Wisdom of the Ages</string>
    <string name="others_e5_quote">"\"Every time an old person dies, a library burns to the ground.\"

- African Proverb"
</string>
    <string name="others_e5_text">Speak to an elderly person in your social circle about their life. Ask them about their best childhood memories. What adventures did they have in their youth? Middle age?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q1_text">How was your experience? What were the conversations about?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q2_text">What is your perception of elderly people in your society? Did that perception change?</string>
    <string name="others_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="others_e6_title">Om mani padme hum..</string>
    <string name="others_e6_quote">"\"God enters by a private door into every individual.\"

-Ralph Waldo Emerson, Philosopher"</string>
    <string name="others_e6_text">Attend a religious ceremony of a different faith than your own. Look for ceremonies that are open to the public and go there with respect, an open-mind, and curiosity.</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q1_text">What have your other experiences with spiritual practices been like?How was it similar or different to your past experiences? What aspects of the ceremony did you find most enlightening?</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q2_text">How were your interactions with the community? Was there anyone you felt a special connection with?</string>
    <string name="others_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with others? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <!--Nature Exercise Strings-->
    <string name="nature_home_title">Nature</string>
    <string name="nature_menu_title">With Nature...</string>

    <string name="nature_e1_title">Hug A Tree!</string>

    <string name="nature_e1_quote">"\"Trees are poems the earth writes upon the sky\"

- Kahlil Gibran, Poet"
    </string>

    <string name="nature_e1_text">"Follow your intuition and find a tree that inspires you (it doesn\’t have to be big, just find any tree that speaks to you). Close your eyes, take a deep long breath, and give the tree a big hug!…"</string>

    <string name="nature_e1_q1_text">Was it your first experience of hugging a tree? Did you do it in a public space, why or why not?</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_q2_text">It is said that hugging a tree helps to make you feel more calm and relaxed. Did you feel those benefits? Would you do it again?</string>
    <string name="nature_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection to nature? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="nature_e2_title">Walk with Nature</string>

    <string name="nature_e2_quote">"\"In every walk with nature one receives far more than one seeks.\"

- John Muir, Conservationist"
    </string>

    <string name="nature_e2_text">Go in nature by yourself with a very minimal predetermined route or length of time. Take your time and pay attention to small details (a mushroom growing, a bird singing, the pattern of a leaf, etc!)</string>

    <string name="nature_e2_q1_text">How was your mindset during the walk? Were you thinking a lot or not at all? What were the thoughts in your head?</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_q2_text">What was the most exciting thing that happened during that walk? Name one thing that you saw, smelled, heard, and touched.</string>
    <string name="nature_e2_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_title">A Child of Nature</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_quote">"\"All through my life, the new sights of Nature made me rejoice like a child.\"

- Marie Curie, Physicist"
</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_text">Try to remember a memory from your childhood that you felt particularly connected with nature. Visualize it the best you can: Where was it? What were the elements of nature ? Who were you with? What were you doing?</string>

    <string name="nature_e3_q1_text">What was the importance of nature during your childhood?</string>
    <string name="nature_e3_q2_text">How did the memory or that particular place shape the relationship that you now have with nature?</string>
    <string name="nature_e3_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e4_title">Do the Earth a Favor</string>

    <string name="nature_e4_quote">"\"We have forgotten how to be good guests, how to walk lightly on the earth as its other creatures do.\"

- Barbara Ward, Economist"</string>

    <string name="nature_e4_text">Walk around your local park or neighborhood and pick up a single piece of trash (or more!) off the ground. Make sure it finds its way to the proper bin! (Remember to compost or recycle if you can.)</string>

    <string name="nature_e4_q1_text">Did you notice a lot (or very little) trash where you were walking? How do you feel about it? When it made it to the bin, what was the first feeling that you had?</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_q2_text">Do you usually pick up trash off the ground? Why or not?</string>
    <string name="nature_e4_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e5_title">Be In Your Elements</string>

    <string name="nature_e5_quote">"\"One way to open your eyes is to ask yourself, \"What if I had never seen this before? What if I knew I would never see it again?\"

- Rachel Carson, Biologist"</string>

    <string name="nature_e5_text">"Connect mindfully with the four elements using all your senses. The four elements are Earth, Water, Fire and Air.

For example, silence your thoughts, and stare at a lit candle, feel the soil with your bare feet, listen to the wind, and smell the ocean."</string>

    <string name="nature_e5_q1_text">Which element did you feel the most connected to? Why?</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_q2_text">Which sense did you naturally use the most to connect with each element?</string>
    <string name="nature_e5_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <string name="nature_e6_title">Adopt a Pet Plant!</string>

    <string name="nature_e6_quote">"\"I grow plants for many reasons: to please my eye or to please my soul, to challenge the elements or to challenge my patience, for novelty or for nostalgia, but mostly for the joy in seeing them grow.\"

- David Hobson, Composer"</string>

    <string name="nature_e6_text">Find a small plant that is seeding in a park, or in the woods. Gently up root it, and grab some of the soil that it was growing in. Bring it home, put it into a cup or jar, try to identify the species and its basic needs, and see what happens!</string>

    <string name="nature_e6_q1_text">Why did you choose this plant? What attracted you to that particular plant?</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_q2_text">Do you feel any emotional connection with the plant now that it’s home?</string>
    <string name="nature_e6_q3_text">"How did this exercise influence your connection to nature?
        Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?"</string>

    <!-- Society Exercises Strings -->
    <string name="society_home_title">Society</string>
    <string name="society_menu_title">With Society...</string>

    <string name="society_e1_title">The Virtual World</string>
    <string name="society_e1_quote">"\"We no longer use technology, we live it.\"

- Michiel Schwarz, Cultural Thinker""</string>
    <string name="society_e1_text">For one full day, be aware of your phone usage. Take a count of each time you check your phone and see how many times you checked it by the end of the day.</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q1_text">What prompts you to check your phone? The device itself (alert, etc)? Something to do to fill an empty moment?</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q2_text">Of all the times that you check your phone, how many would you say were really necessary?</string>
    <string name="society_e1_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e2_title">Our Attachment to Money</string>
    <string name="society_e2_quote">"\"Money is a strange business. People who haven't got it aim for it strongly. People who have are full of troubles.\"

- Ayrton Senna, Car Racer"
    </string>
    <string name="society_e2_text">Think of your relationship with money. Focus on your feelings around it, and your initial emotional reaction to your current financial situation.</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q1_text">What is more important to you than money? What would you not give up for any price in the world?</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q2_text">What would you consider “enough”? How big would your bank account have to be that when you see it, you feel safe and free to take opportunities?</string>
    <string name="society_e2_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e3_title">Your Political Voice</string>
    <string name="society_e3_quote">"\"Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed citizens can change the world; indeed, it's the only thing that ever has.\"

- Margaret Mead, Anthropologist"</string>
    <string name="society_e3_text">Local governments often have a much bigger effect on your life than the national one. Attend a local city council meeting, and try to meet your representative. Is there any important issue you could talk with your local representative or fellow citizens about?</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q1_text">What issues did they discuss? Was there anything about the process that stood out to you?</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q2_text">Did you like your representative? How could you work with them to address the issues you feel concerned about?</string>
    <string name="society_e3_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e4_title"> In the Shoes of…</string>
    <string name="society_e4_quote">"\"There is no such thing as a single-issue struggle, because we do not live single-issue lives.\"

-Audre Lorde, Feminist activist"
    </string>
    <string name="society_e4_text">Try to imagine yourself in someone else’s shoes : a person who is of a different ethnicity, sex, gender, socio-economic background, religion, sexual orientation, disability status, etc. You can think about somebody you know, or a fictional person. What would their daily lived experience feel like?</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q1_text">What kind of invisible social structures and/or preconceptions are favorable or limiting for that person?</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q2_text">What are the differences and similarities between you and the life of this other person?</string>
    <string name="society_e4_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e5_title">Every Bit Counts</string>
    <string name="society_e5_quote">"\"It's vitally important to help each other. No, we can't walk in each other's shoes, but we can walk side-by-side and support each other.\"

- Michele Sullivan, Social Impact Adviser"
    </string>
    <string name="society_e5_text">Sign up to make a small monthly donation (whatever you can afford) to a charity that advocates for a cause that you support. Use your heart and your head to make sure of the validity of the organization. A monthly donation makes you a real member of these organizations.</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q1_text">How do you feel about giving to a cause on a regular basis? Do you feel more committed to it?</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q2_text">Do you think you’ll participate or become more involved with the issue or the organization over time? How?</string>
    <string name="society_e5_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

    <string name="society_e6_title">Do Good Works</string>
    <string name="society_e6_quote">"\"Life’s most persistent and urgent question is, what are you doing for others?\"

- Martin Luther King Jr., Civil Rights Leader"</string>
    <string name="society_e6_text">A tried and true classic to feel good and meet great people! Find a cause and organization you care about, and volunteer for a day. Even if it’s just once, you certainly won’t forget the experience.</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q1_text">Where did you choose to volunteer? What was the work like?</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q2_text">Did you build good relationships? Did you feel connected with the other volunteers? Your community as a whole?</string>
    <string name="society_e6_q3_text">How did this exercise influence your connection with society? Are there any insights or strong feelings that you will remember from this exercise?</string>

</resources>
